sleepapnea-treatments.net 2012-10-27

# Privacy policy sleep apnea treatments blog | Sleep apnea treatments

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of **[sleep apnea treatments](http://sleepapnea-treatments.net/ "Sleep apnea treatments")** website visitors is important to us. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. Log files as with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.

The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Comcast), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

We do not use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our _sleep apnea treatments_ blog. We do use third party advertisements to support our site.

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

If you believe that this policy is inadequate or needs changing please [let us know](http://sleepapnea-treatments.net/contact-us/ "Contact sleep apnea treatments blog").

The policy in this sleep apnea treatments blog may be changed from time to time without prior notice.

Comments are closed.
